"use strict";(self.webpackChunkreact_quiz=self.webpackChunkreact_quiz||[]).push([[697],{697:function(e,t,n){n.r(t);t.default=[{questionType:"TrueORFalse",question:"\u8e29\u6c34\u6642\u53ea\u8981\u4fdd\u6301\u53e3\u9f3b\u9732\u51fa\u6c34\u9762\u5373\u53ef\uff0c\u624b\u8173\u52d5\u4f5c\u5b9c\u7de9\u6162\u8eab\u9ad4\u4fdd\u6301\u7565\u5411\u524d\u50be\uff0c\u8eab\u9ad4\u5118\u91cf\u653e\u9b06\uff0c\u624b\u8173\u4e4b\u52d5\u4f5c\u8981\u5354\u8abf\u4e00\u81f4\u3002",answers:[{type:"T",content:"O"},{type:"F",content:"X"}]},{questionType:"TrueORFalse",question:"\u8e29\u6c34\u6642\u8eab\u9ad4\u76f4\u7acb\u5448\u300c\u5927\u300d\u5f62\uff0c\u5229\u7528\u8eab\u9ad4\u66f2\u6298\u9762\u7a4d\uff0c\u4ee5\u589e\u52a0\u6d6e\u529b\u3002",answers:[{type:"F",content:"O"},{type:"T",content:"X"}]},{questionType:"TrueORFalse",question:"\u8e29\u6c34\u53ef\u5206\u70ba\u526a\u5200\u5f0f\u3001\u8173\u8e0f\u8eca\u5f0f\u3001\u86d9\u5f0f\u53ca\u652a\u86cb\u5f0f\u8e29\u6c34\u3002",answers:[{type:"T",content:"O"},{type:"F",content:"X"}]},{questionType:"TrueORFalse",question:"\u8e29\u6c34\u53c8\u7a31\u7acb\u6cf3\uff0c\u662f\u6700\u57fa\u672c\u53ca\u5be6\u7528\u4e4b\u81ea\u6551\u8207\u6551\u751f\u6280\u8853\u4e4b\u4e00\u3002",answers:[{type:"T",content:"O"},{type:"F",content:"X"}]},{questionType:"TrueORFalse",question:"\u8e29\u6c34\u4ee5\u4e0b\u80a2\u7684\u52d5\u4f5c\u70ba\u4e3b\uff0c\u624b\u90e8\u53ef\u5e6b\u52a9\u5e73\u8861\u53ca\u4e0a\u6d6e\u6216\u662f\u5c07\u7269\u54c1\u652f\u6490\u5728\u6c34\u9762\u4e0a\u3002",answers:[{type:"T",content:"O"},{type:"F",content:"X"}]},{questionType:"TrueORFalse",question:"\u8e29\u6c34\u6642\uff0c\u8eab\u9ad4\u4f4d\u7f6e\u662f\u5411\u5f8c\u4ef0\u7684\uff0c\u53ef\u4ee5\u8b93\u53e3\u9f3b\u4fdd\u6301\u5728\u6c34\u9762\u4e0a\u3002",answers:[{type:"F",content:"O"},{type:"T",content:"X"}]},{questionType:"TrueORFalse",question:"\u624b\u90e8\u6416\u6ad3\u7684\u52d5\u4f5c\u53ef\u589e\u9032\u5347\u529b\uff0c\u7dad\u6301\u8eab\u9ad4\u7684\u5e73\u8861\u3002",answers:[{type:"T",content:"O"},{type:"F",content:"X"}]},{questionType:"multipleChoice",question:"\u8e29\u6c34\u4e0d\u542b",answers:[{type:"F",content:"\u86d9\u5f0f\u8e29\u6c34"},{type:"F",content:"\u526a\u5f0f\u8e29\u6c34"},{type:"T",content:"\u942e\u5200\u5f0f\u8e29\u6c34"},{type:"F",content:"\u8173\u8e0f\u8eca\u5f0f\u8e29\u6c34\u3002"}]},{questionType:"multipleChoice",question:"\u8e29\u6c34\u6642\u53ea\u8981\u4fdd\u6301\u53e3\u9f3b\u9732\u51fa\u6c34\u9762\u5373\u53ef\uff0c\u624b\u8173\u52d5\u4f5c\u5b9c\u7de9\u6162\u8eab\u9ad4\u4fdd\u6301\u7565\u5411",answers:[{type:"F",content:"\u76f4\u7acb"},{type:"T",content:"\u524d\u50be"},{type:"F",content:"\u5f8c\u4ef0 \uff0c\u8eab\u9ad4\u5118\u91cf\u653e\u9b06\uff0c\u624b\u8173\u4e4b\u52d5\u4f5c\u8981\u5354\u8abf\u4e00\u81f4\u3002"}]},{questionType:"multipleChoice",question:"\u8e29\u6c34\u6642\u53e3\u9f3b\u9732\u51fa\u6c34\u9762\u5373\u53ef\uff0c\u96d9\u624b\u5728\u80f8\u524d\u5411\u5169\u5074\u505a\u6416\u6ad3\u5f0f\u5212\u6c34\uff0c\u8173\u90e8\u82e5\u63a1\u86d9\u5f0f\u52d5\u4f5c\u8005\u7a31\u70ba",answers:[{type:"T",content:"\u86d9\u5f0f\u8e29\u6c34"},{type:"F",content:"\u8173\u8e0f\u8eca\u5f0f\u8e29\u6c34"},{type:"F",content:"\u526a\u5f0f\u8e29\u6c34\u3002"}]},{questionType:"multipleChoice",question:"\u82e5\u8173\u4f5c\u524d\u5f8c\u526a\u5200\u5f0f\u52d5\u4f5c\u8e29\u6c34\uff0c\u4f7f\u8eab\u9ad4\u6f02\u6d6e\u8005\u7a31\u70ba",answers:[{type:"F",content:"\u86d9\u5f0f\u8e29\u6c34"},{type:"F",content:"\u8173\u8e0f\u8eca\u5f0f\u8e29\u6c34"},{type:"T",content:"\u526a\u5f0f\u8e29\u6c34\u3002"}]}]}}]);
//# sourceMappingURL=697.d36e9291.chunk.js.map